* Apps
* Developers
* Legal
* [\[email protected\]](https://counter.social/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

.

.

.

.

Privacy Policy
==============

### What information do we collect?

We collect minimal information from you when you register on our site and gather data when you participate in the forum by reading, writing, and evaluating the content shared here. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site without registering. Your e-mail address will be verified by an email containing a unique link. If that link is visited, we know that you control the e-mail address. When registered and posting, we record the IP address that the post originated from. We also may retain server logs which include the IP address of every request to our server.

### What do we use the information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* • To personalize your experience — your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
* • To improve our site — we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on feedback we receive from you.
* • To improve customer service — to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### What is your data retention policy?

* • Retain server logs containing the IP address of all requests to this server no more than 90 days.
* • Retain the IP addresses, metdata, unencrypted comms associated with users no more than 90 days.\*

\* Only if contacted by a law enforcement agency and only in accordance with our [Law Enforcement Request Policy.](https://counter.social/leareqs.html)

### Do we use cookies?

Yes, but no more than any other site. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow). These cookies enable the site to recognize your browser and, if you have a registered account, associate it with your registered account. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law in accordance and compliance with our [Law Enforcement Request Policy](https://counter.social/leareqs.html), or to enforce our site policies, protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Artificial Intelligence, Large Language Model and Translation Services

All CounterSocial AI (for example: our 'Alfred' AI Assistant), Large language Model, and Language Translation elements operate with your privacy in mind, and as such NO user or personally identifying information is collected. Only the raw information necessary to complete the transaction is transmitted. Further, all systems covered in this section are opt-in or activated with a 'wake word'. None of these elements have the ability to monitor CounterSocial users or harvest their interactions for the purposes of training any internal or external Large Language Models or other AI technology.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Our site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old. If you are under the age of 13, per the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act) do not use this site.

### Online privacy policy scope

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our site and not to information collected offline.

### Payment Processing

All financial transactions and payments to or from CounterSocial are handled by a professional dedicated 3rd party payments processor. No payment details are stored on CounterSocial infrastructure, at any time. This protects both the user and CounterSocial.

### Right to be forgotten

The right to be forgotten is the right to have private information about a person be removed from Internet services, searches and other directories under some circumstances. CounterSocial respects a user's Right to Be Forgotten. As such, by default all user content is protected from web crawlers, archivers, search engines, and other 3rd party scrapers around the web. Users may enable their Public Landing Page if they so wish. Further, in order to combat and deter cyber-stalking and harassment the content search scope is limited to usernames, hashtags and posts a user has made, was mentioned in or interacted with via favoriting, replying or boosting. Moreover, when a user is suspended or deletes their own account, all content and account information is irrevocably removed from our infrastructure. Upon account deletion, only the username is retained in order for us to keep it flagged as no longer available to prevent later impersonation or brand hijacking by nefarious actors. Usernames are non-reusable, non-recoverable and non-recyclable, except in cases of brand impersonation for this reason.

### your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes to this privacy policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

.

**SEE RELATED:** [Terms of Service](https://counter.social/terms.html) and [Privacy Policy](https://counter.social/privacy.html) and [DMCA Policy](https://counter.social/dmca.html) and [GDPR Policy](https://counter.social/gdpr.html) and [CCPA Policy](https://counter.social/ccpa.html) and [LEA Policy](https://counter.social/leareqs.html) and [License](https://counter.social/license.html)

This document was last updated July 27 2023.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |

© CounterSocial all rights reserved.
